liveforlivemusic.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy

Live For Live Music is driven by a group of like-minded individuals who crave live music experiences all year round. Delivering show reviews, supporting photo/video/audio media, exclusive features, and contests directly to your devices demonstrates L4LM’s distinct desire to share this obsession with our fans. However, maintaining the privacy of the personal information you entrust to us is just as important. This Privacy Policy explains how we use and share personal information we collect through LiveForLiveMusic.com.

By using LiveForLiveMusic.com, subscribing to our newsletter, or using any of our other products or services, you are accepting the practices we describe here.

L4LM collects personal information, which you provide voluntarily, and non-personal usage information, which we collect using cookies and other technologies as you browse our sites or use our products or services.

If you want to receive our email newsletter, participate in any of our contests or promotions, fill out a questionnaire or survey or engage in certain other activities on our sites, you will need to provide us with certain personal information. The specific information will vary depending on the activity, and may include your name, email address, mailing address, birth date and gender. If you’re not interested in participating, that’s totally fine–you are still free to browse our sites–but if you want to interact more deeply with what L4LM has to offer, you will need to sign up and provide us with the requested information.

In order to pay for L4LM products or services, you will need to provide valid billing and credit card information (your credit card number and expiration date, billing address, etc.). This information will only be shared with third parties who perform credit card processing, subscription fulfillment or other tasks required to deliver the purchased product or service. In some cases, the third parties we have contracted to perform the service will collect this information from you directly.

We also collect information that does not identify you personally, but gives us data about your computer and how you use our websites. This information includes your IP address, your browser type, operating system, the date and time you access the site, and the website that referred you to our site.

We collect and store information using “cookies.” A cookie is a small text file stored on your computer, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, the web server asks your browser for permission to store this file, or “drop the cookie” on your computer or mobile device, which we then use to recognize you when you visit our sites. Cookies link to information we store regarding pages you have viewed or features you have used.

Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent on the websites, and the websites you visited just before and just after coming to our sites. We may also use “web beacons,” which track your use of our websites in order to provide you with a more personalized experience the next time you visit.

You can configure your browser’s settings regarding cookies by selecting “Internet Options” (IE), “Options” (Firefox and Chrome) or “Preferences” (Safari) or in the “Tools” menu of your browser. If you want, you can prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether. However, some aspects of our websites will not function properly if you do not accept cookies.

Live For Live Music’s advertisers and advertising vendors display targeted advertisements. Although we do not provide any personal information to the advertiser or advertising vendor, by interacting with or clicking on an ad, you acknowledge the possibility that the advertiser may assume you meet the targeting criteria used.

In addition to our cookies and tracking technologies, advertisers and advertising vendors that serve ads on our websites may use their own. Their use of the non-personal information they collect is governed by their own privacy policies, and their practices are not under our control.

L4LM works with Google & PubWise for the delivery of advertisements to our websites. The non-personally-identifiable information they collect about your visits to our websites may be used to provide advertisements about goods and services they believe (based upon your previous behavior) may be of interest to you.

Please be aware that advertisers have links on our sites that take you to other sites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Use of the information collected by these third party sites will be governed by their own privacy policies, and L4LM does not assume any responsibility for their actions. If you have any questions about how a third party handles personal information, please contact them directly.

* * *

In general, Live For Live Music may use information that we collect about you in the following ways:

• to communicate with you by email about topics that we think may be of interest to you  
• to help us develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests  
• to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes  
• to process payment for products/services  
• to deliver the products/services you request  
• to analyze your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content (or products, services or content offered by others on our websites)  
• to enforce our terms and conditions  
• to protect against or identify fraudulent transactions  
• to generally manage our business.

Live For Live Music may disclose your personal information to companies we engage as contractors or agents to perform services for us, such as providing email marketing or administering a sweepstake or contest. We share information with these contractors only to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations.

We may also share your personal information collected in connection with a service, contest, sweepstakes, promotion or questionnaire with the third party partners or sponsors, or otherwise in accordance with the rules of the event. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of these events, as they may contain additional important information about a sponsor’s or other third party’s use of your personal information.

We may also disclose your personal information if we are legally compelled to do so. In other words, when the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary or appropriate to address potential or actual injury or interference with the rights, property or operations of L4LM, our users or others. Finally, if we undergo a merger or acquisition, or sell or otherwise transfer substantially all the assets of L4LM, Inc., or relating to any website that we own or operate or any product or service that we offer, your personal information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers, and investors, for general business analysis purposes. This aggregated data does not contain any personal information.

At any time, you can manage your email preferences and other aspects of your profile, including opting out of receiving newsletters and promotional emails from L4LM, by clicking on the link at the bottom of any email that says “update subscription preferences.” You may also opt-out from such emails completely by clicking on the link at the bottom of any email that says “unsubscribe from this list.”

Even if you have unsubscribed from receiving promotional emails from L4LM, we may send you other types of important email communications, such as customer service communications and announcements, purchase notifications and confirmations, administrative notices, and surveys. You cannot opt out of receiving such service communications.

We use industry standard technology and services to protect and secure your information. We will never initiate any email communication with you that requests your private information. In general, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Please contact L4LM customer support (kendall@liveforlivemusic.com) if you have any questions or concerns.

L4LM reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice explaining the changes. You will be deemed to have accepted such change if you continue to use our website after the revised policy has been posted.
